Welcome back, Teddy. Uh, just wanted to
know, uh, just what keeps what keeps
drawing you back to this place? Is it
Dan Cample or just what is it about
these Lions that keep you coming back?
>> Um, it's a combination of things and,
um, you know, I'm excited to be back for
the third time. Um, you know, you talk
about the relationship I have with Dan
Campbell. Um, the players in this locker
room, um, this city, um, they welcome
myself, my family. Um, I know a lot of
the coaches on this staff been with
throughout my career. So, it's just it's
a match and I'm excited to just continue
my journey
>> Dave.
>> Hey, Teddy. I just want to welcome back
first of all, um, just want to build off
that a little bit more, too. you know,
the first time we saw you, right, we
thought you were done and you came back
and and now you're you're still going.
What What does the future hold for you?
How much longer do you want to do this?
Um, and why do you why do you keep
loving to do this?
>> Um, I honestly
just it's like I I visited a fountain of
youth or something this past year and
um, you know, that fire has been lit and
I don't know what it is. is I don't know
if it's my my my children or just being
back home, but it's just something in me
that's just like, man, you know what? I
could do this again. Um, and the past
couple years I was one foot in, one foot
out, you know, contemplating retirement,
contemplating playing, coaching, doing
all these different things. And now it's
like, okay, I've coached. I know what
that's like. You know, I've been
retired. I know what that's like. But,
uh, like I just want to keep playing
ball. And um I've been in the gym down
in South Florida with Jonathan Taylor,
Bree Hall, you know, Hard Time, Maurice
Alexander, just being around these young
guys and you know, reminding myself
that, you know, I I tricked myself
thinking that I'm old. You know, I'm not
old. You know, I got so much left in the
tank that um I can continue just playing
in this league and I I got so much left
to offer this game. I just want to
continue to just contribute in every
aspect that I can. Did those things, you
know, um, stir the love even more,
right? Being away from it coaching,
being away from it in retirement. Does
that make you realize like how much it
you miss it? How much it means to you, I
guess?
>> Yeah. Yeah, that definitely made me
realize how much I missed it, especially
everything I went through last year um
with the coaching and um, you know,
things happen for a reason, but uh, I'm
just excited that, you know, I get to
continue year 13 now and just continue
to try to make an impact in this league.
Last thing on that topic, the um do you
still whenever you're done, do you still
intend to coach again? And would it
still be high school or or would it be
somewhere else?
>> Uh Dave, I think, man, if I do get into
coaching again, I think I'mma probably
go private school.
>> Yeah,
>> it's less headaches. Um that's for 10
years from now. We'll talk about that
again.
>> All right, sounds good. And then very
last thing, just on this offense, you
know, it's it's mostly the same but a
little bit different than the last time
you were here. So, just kind of your
expectations for the season and kind of
when you look around at the talent, what
do you what do you still think about
what what you have in that locker room?
>> And uh you know, you cut the tape on and
you see those guys flying around last
year and um you know, things happen
throughout the course of a season and um
no team stays the same and um
it's a such a talented group though. you
know, there's still so many playmakers
across the board and I think for those
guys, I think last year left a bad taste
in their mouth not making the playoffs.
So, I know, you know, they're the guys
that I know and they're the guys that I
met two years ago and played on the same
team with two years ago and I know that
they'll bounce back. They'll come back
even hungrier. Um, I know those guys are
working their tails off this offseason
and I know they can't wait to get back
out there and just redeem themselves.
>> Great. Thank you. Welcome back again,
Teddy.
>> I appreciate it, Dave.
>> Tim,
>> welcome back, Teddy. Uh, I was just
curious, you've been a starter in this
league and and you know the value of of
having, you know, some veteran guys in
that room with you. I'm just curious
what your relationship with with Jared
Goff is and and what's the value of of
having veteran guys in that quarterback
room more than just beyond just the
starter?
>> Oh, man. Just having that veteran
presence, whether it's a starter,
backup, third string guy, is is so
valuable for a team. Um especially when
you have guys who had a ton of playing
experience. Um it's an extra coach in
the room. It's an extra pair of eyes for
the starter. Um and that relationship
for Jared and I, you know, I consider I
think Jared would agree. We're kind of
like ghosting Tommy off power. Um you
know, it's a dynamic duo. So, uh, I'm
happy to be back in the room with him,
Brew, and you know, Mike, and, uh,
whoever else you know what's in store.
>> Thanks. Welcome back.
>> Thanks.
>> All right, let's go. Last one. Rich.
>> Hey, Teddy. You uh, you mentioned having
the fire back a little bit. What did you
miss most? Was it just competing, being
in the locker room? Like, what did you
miss most over the the year or so you
were out?
>> I miss competing.
um whether it's in practice um two years
ago competing against you know this
defense I know a lot has changed but you
know two years ago competing in practice
against these guys um get an opportunity
to compete in the preseason um you know
that that fire to just compete and and
want to go out there and just excel and
help others as well though you know I
always been that type of player who just
want to see others have success and um I
always felt like as a quarterback, we
play a huge role in other other success.
So, you know, if I could just go out
there and help, you know, a sixround
wide receiver have a a four or five year
career, undrafted free agent, you know,
get four or five years out of the
league, you know, from just competing
with them throughout the spring,
preseason training camp, whether we get
reps in the regular season. Um, that's
just something I look forward to